hi Hawks Motorsports team my name is
Christy gupton and I'm going to review
with you the suite of ancillary and
voluntary benefits available to you at
work through Sun
Life some of you may have similar plans
enforced through all state I hope to
help you compare and contrast these
sunlife plans to the Allstate plan so
that you can determine which plans are
best value for you and your family first
off notice that the sunlife policy
number is located at the top of this
page first let's start with your new
dental plan it covers the same types of
dental services you're used
to this dental plan covers up to $1,000
worth of preventive basic and major
Dental Services you'll see on this page
which types of dental work is
categorized as
preventive
basic and
major here are a few frequently asked
questions like how do I find a dentist
or do I have to file a
claim this is an important page to read
over as you consider What dental
services are needed this
year if you don't think you want to
enroll this time but may wait until next
year be cautious there are waiting
periods and benefit limitations for
those who wait to enroll in dental until
later here is a look at your weekly
Dental rates because of the generous
amount Hawks Motorsports is paying on
your behalf
it makes your part extremely affordable
Hawks Motorsports is paying 70% of the
employee only tier and 60% of the spouse
and children
coverage more and more insurance
companies are moving away from printed
Dental ID cards for a while you will
need to use this easy start flyer it's
self-explanatory but here are a few
items to pay attention to First the
policy number that your dental coverage
is under is right here second the phone
number that your provider should call to
be navigated through the claims filing
process and lastly a very easy to
understand process is explained right
here for your
provider now let's talk about vision
insurance insurance if you already wear
glasses or may need a comprehensive
Vision exam this year vision insurance
may be just the thing for
you your annual eye exam is covered you
pay $10 co-pays and the vision plan pays
the rest if you need eyeglasses you pay
a $25 co-pay and the vision plan pays
the rest you have $130 allowance for
frame
but if you'd rather wear contacts you
have $130 allowance for
those here's a frequently asked
questions page for your vision plan
questions like how do I locate a vssp i
doctor or can I buy glasses or contacts
online read over this thoroughly as you
consider what Vision Care you need this
year vision insurance is 100% voluntary
but the weekly premiums are very
affordable you will not receive an ID
card for your vision plan just use this
page in the Box labeled using your
vision plan to locate a vssp network I
doctor now let's talk about life
insurance this is a very important part
of your employee benefits package buying
life insurance at work is the most
affordable way to get the highest amount
of coverage at the lowest price based on
your earnings you can choose up to
$500,000 in group term life however you
can easily enroll in
$100,000 without having to answer any
health
questions here are some frequently asked
questions about voluntary group term
life coverage questions like do I need
to answer any help questions to enroll
or can I increase my coverage at a later
date read over this page carefully as
you make your selection on the next
page first this grid shows the weekly
premiums for the coverage you have
available to you locate your age bracket
at the top of the grid then follow the
coverage amounts down the left column
until you find the amount you wish to
enroll in remember you can choose up to
$100,000 of group term life face amount
without having to answer any health
questions similarly this page shows
weekly premium amounts if you want to
include coverage for your spouse or
children let's move on to short-term
disability remember your bills don't
stop just because you're hurt or sick
you need to to have disability insurance
to make sure you keep money coming in
for everyday Necessities this short-term
disability policy pays 60% of your gross
pay up to $1,500 a week it pays for up
to 25 weeks if you are hurt off the job
or if you get
sick it's important to read about
pre-existing conditions and how to file
a claim
here's how disability insurance premiums
are
calculated enter 60% of your weekly
earnings in this area then divide that
number by 10 then multiply that number
by the rate associated with your current
age this is your monthly cost now let's
convert that to weekly costs by going to
this
row put put your monthly cost here
multiply by 12 that's your annual
premium lastly divide that number by
52 this is your weekly
cost long-term disability is very
similar it begins if you exhaust your
short-term disability starting after 180
days of being disabled and lasts up to
so Social Security normal retirement age
based on the severity of your
disability here are the frequently asked
questions for long-term disability
insurance now let's calculate your
weekly cost for long-term disability
insurance first start with 60% of your
monthly earnings then divide by 10 then
multiply that number by the rate
associated with your
age that is your monthly cost now let's
convert that to weekly put your monthly
cost in this box and then multiply by 12
to get your annual cost and divide by 52
to get your weekly
cost now that you've enrolled in dental
vision life and disability let's talk
about two other options
accident coverage and critical illness
coverage let's talk about accident
coverage first this covers you 24 hours
a day anywhere in the
world let's say there was an accident
and someone broke their arm if they'd
enrolled in the high plan their accident
policy would pay
$1,500 if they needed surgery to repair
their arm
then the policy would also pay
additional money for x-rays Hospital
Services the actual
surgery this plan also pays out a
minimum of $50 each year whether you've
had an accident or not if you're getting
your annual screenings done at your
doctor's office then you're eligible for
that Wellness
benefit here are the frequently asked
questions about the accident policy
and here are the weekly deductions for
the accident
policy okay here's the last plan to
review this is a critical illness policy
and like the name implies it pays up to
a $20,000 face amount for critical
illnesses here is a very extensive list
of critical illnesses that may generate
that payment or a portion of that
payment just like the accident policy
even if you never have a claim to file
on this critical illness policy you
still receive a $50 Wellness benefit
every year for getting your annual
screenings
done be sure to read over the frequently
asked questions
page here are the age banded weekly
premium amounts for the critical illness
policy based on your age
bracket as well as the weekly premium
amounts for your spouse and or
children these next three pages are
important definitions terms and
exclusions associated with your Sun Life
package of ancillary and voluntary
employee benefits it's important to
review these
Pages here's page two of the terms and
exclusions and this is just a disclaimer
about the availability of these plans
across the
country these next two pages detail when
you might need to use the evidence of
insurability forms this will only be
used if you are applying for more than
the guaranteed issue amount of life
insurance or if you wave any part of
this package this year but change your
mind and want to enroll in the future
you'll need to use the evidence of
insurability form for
that and this is page two of the
evidence of insurability
form every employee will use the
enrollment form to indicate if you do or
don't want to enroll in the sunlife
coverage I will help you complete this
form next week and I will submit it on
your
behalf this is this is page two of the
application this is where you'll
indicate who your beneficiaries will
be and the last page is where I enter my
information we are almost done as a
customer covered by a sunlife policy
you'll want to establish a sunlife
account on your smartphone it'll add the
sunlife app to your phone that'll allow
you to carry a digital version of your
dental ID card with you at all times and
answer claims and customer service
questions quickly and easily just scan
the QR code to get the download
started and finally this is me Christy
gupton I'm here to advise you and
provide great customer service
throughout the process I'm here for you
so just contact me anytime you need to